affiliatefanpages.com 2015-02-02

# Privacy Policy | affiliatefanpages.com

## **Privacy Policy**

**1.  Information on visitors**

As you use this website, a cookie may be downloaded onto your computer.

Cookies can be useful things, and are used for functions like ‘Remember me’ to save you having to input your details every time you visit.

Any use of cookies on this site is only for the benefit of enhancing our service to you.

****2\. What is a cookie?****

When you enter a site your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie … [see Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) for more info.

Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used.

See more below in section 5 which relates to Google adverts on this site.

****You  can set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie  
is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time.

Remember, if you haven’t set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse our site anonymously until such time as you register for this web site’s services. ** ** ****

**3\. Use and storage of your personal information**

We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in  
accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

Any information given via this site will be:

Fairly and lawfully processed

Processed for limited purposes

Adequate, relevant and not excessive

Accurate and up to date

Not kept for longer than is necessary

Processed in line with your rights

Secure

More information can be found via <http://www.ico.gov.uk/>

**4.  Google adverts**

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

Users may opt out of the use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_cookies.html).

You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, you can point your visitors to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Please note the following:

**Routine  information collection**

a) All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

b) Where necessary this website uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

c) Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Controlling your privacy**

d) You can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**5\. Access to your personal information**

****You  have the right to request a copy of the personal information this website  
holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. (We charge £10  
for information requests.)

Please address requests via the form at the bottom of this page in the first instance. ** ** ****

**6 . Users 16 and under** If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian’s permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to this website.

If you haven’t got this consent you are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

**7\. Remarketing**

This site uses remarketing.

This means that once you visit this site, a cookie will be placed which allows me to market you you via participating 3rd party web sites.

3rd party vendors, such as Google, will be able to serve our ads to you across the internet.

Remember, You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, you can point your visitors to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**8\. Registration with the Information Commissioner’s Office**

Paul Teague Marketing Ltd , which operates  this website, is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 as holding data for 2 purposes:

a) Advertising, Marketing and Public Relations  
b) Administration of Membership Records

More information can be found via <http://www.ico.gov.uk/>

Registration number: Z2876371

**9)  ‘No spam’ policy** ****

When you sign up for any service on this website you will be asked to confirm that it was you who requested the service before it is delivered.

You will also be given a chance to unsubscribe at any time.

You will only receive the service that you have requested plus any other communications associated with that service.

We will not pass your details on to any third parties at any time.
